You made it out again!
Yay!
But since I don't want to be a bad host, I will do it too, not with the latex one.
I'll get into the spandex suit.
I'll get into this one, you'll get into this one.
Okay!
I'll do it if you do it.
Okay, you already did it, it's not fair.
Okay let's do the comparison.
How fast can you get into that?
I don't think you'll need my help because I tried it before, it's pretty easy.
Yeah, I think it's easier.
And I think you have like pockets for the arms in this one.
Really?
Yes.
Oh yeah.
You can see the stitching here.
Well, that was pretty fast with the legs already.
Now arms.
This is for the arms.
Yeah, you have to put your arms inside and then I'll pull it over your shoulders.
Oh, this is so easy.
Why didn't we do the latex one again?
That was quick.
Yeah?
Yeah.
How do you feel compared to the latex one?
It's comfy and it was really fast, but I think I like the latex one a little bit more.
Why?
I don't know, the feeling was a little bit better.
It was tighter?
Yeah.
Apparently.
And yeah.
There's a hood.
Are you okay with me putting on the hood over your head?
Yeah.
Yeah?
If not, just scream.
No.
I have to watch out for the ponytail though.
So I figured the best way to put hoods on is if you tip the head back.
Yeah.
Yes.
And now like forward again.
You okay?
Mhm.
Yeah.
I'll just leave the ponytail outside I guess.
Haha.
Alright.
Hello, can you see me?
No, I just see a little bit of light.
Little bit of light?
Yeah, but that's all.
Yeah.
How do you feel?
It's a little bit weird.
Why?
It's a new feeling, so because I'm a little bit older, I'm a little bit more of a
It's a new feeling, so... because I can't see anything.
But you can obviously talk, so it's not that restricting.
No.
You can move your mouth and like...
Feels so weird talking to you like this.
Feels weird too for me.
So now you can actually see the ponytail. I'll help you turn around again.
You just told me something really interesting off camera.
Yeah.
Yeah. Do you remember?
I feel like a mummy.
Like a mummy.
Maybe you're just awake from ancient... who knows.
Yeah.
By the way, I'm wearing a catsuit in the same material.
I think it looks really cool together if I see the two of us in the mirror.
I'll release you from the hood so we can talk again.
Eye to eye. I just don't want to hurt your hair.
Yeah, that's fine.
so much light. I'm gonna fix the hair. There you are again. So before I completely
release the eye guard into the second drawer I'll try at least. By the way you have a zipper here
in the crotch area. Oh yeah. Yeah. Interesting. I'll just put it over my catsuit. So we have a
double layer of spandex. This one is one without hood but with the same pockets
for the arms on the inside. Alright. It feels like... do you know the kids game from
kids birthday? Sackhüpfen? Yeah. I feel like I'm getting into a Sackhüpfen contest now.
Yeah, that's right. Whatever.
Alright, now I need help from the lovely person doing the camera stuff.
Because I can't really close the zipper myself and you're not helping either.
I can't help you, sorry.
I feel like this would be a really weird comic situation.
Two of us looking like this talking to each other now we have to say something funny.
Great.
Let's do fun stuff because no one can move.
No.
Actually, can you move your arms?
Yeah, just a little bit. My hands.
Yeah.
So mine doesn't have a crotch zipper. Mine is also standard size.
While the one you're wearing is made to my measurements actually.
But I think it fits you really good too.
Yeah.
And now we just have to figure out how to get out of it again.
Hmm.
Yeah.
Maybe we need help again.
I think so.
No idea, but no cookies for me.
I'm better at it than you.
But...
Okay.
Back to topic.
I wanted to say something about the hood
because your hood is completely closed
but you also have the option to
do it like open eyes or mouth or whatever just click on the homepage of
Brighton shiny and have a look at different options and I think we're done
here let's have pizza yeah because I'm hungry
yeah me too thank you very much for joining me today I thank you it was
really great and I had a lot of fun I hope to see you again here all right
let's go